Viewers all over the world,
it is time to talk to your body;
it is time to talk to your soul and spirit.
Your body, listen: every organ that is not functioning in your system,
in your faculties, right now by the blood of Jesus and the power of the Holy Ghost,
Holy Ghost!
In the name of Jesus, begin to function.
My kidney begin to function!
My liver begin to function!
My blood begin to function!
In the name of Jesus.
Those of you under the influence of this voice,
I declare that spirit is not of God, wanted!
Wanted!
You evil spirit, vacate!
I say vacate!
Their body is not your temple.
Right now begin vacate them!
Begin to quit them!
I say quit!
I command you wanted!
I command you out! I say out out!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua, touch the screen by faith in Jesus' Name
The will of God be done.
Every will that is not the will of God...out!
Say: "Every will that is not the will of God...out!"
Let the will of God be done.
Every will that is not of God...
every will that is not of Jesus..
out! In the name of Jesus.
Are you on the sick bed?
Are you in a helpless situation?
What is the situation that you are in?
Are you in a coma, or on a sick bed?
Whatever state you are in, Jesus
knows better .
I command every organ...begin to function in the name of Jesus!
By the power of the Holy Ghost, every organ begins to function.
Every organ...begin to function by the power of the Holy Ghost.
Every organ begin to function in the name of Jesus!
Pray along with prophet T.B Joshua, touch the screen by faith in Jesus Name
Declare it is well with m should!
Declare,"it is well with my spirit."
Declare, "it is well with my body."
Declare, "it is well with my career."
Declare, "it is well with my home."
It is well, in Jesus name!
It is well!
Give thanks to God.
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click to here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest: prophecies, deliverances, service and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church Of All Nations
Emmanuel TV...changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.